bridedressup.net 2013-09-20

# PRIVACY POLICY -

**PRIVACY POLICY -[bridedressup.net](http://bridedressup.net/)**

bridedressup.net is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. We respect the privacy concerns of visitors to bridedressup.net. 

**Information we collect and how we use it  
**On your visit to our website there is certain information that we collect from traffic references of hosting servers and from cookies.

_From traffic references of hosting servers_ – every time you visit a website, there is certain information you make available for collection such as IP address, time of visit, location, internet domain, type of browser and operating system used to access our site, pages you visit, if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website etc. We, like other operators, collect this information and use it for visitors’ statistics and to improve our services to you.

_From Cookies_ – the sole purpose of cookies is to enhance your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by Web sites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Web site that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from bridedressup.net is only accessible by the bridedressup.net Web site. This information enables us to run our affiliate programs, allows customized advertising and offers other operational site activities. Most of browsers are set to accept cookies. But if you prefer, you can reset your browser so as to let you know whenever you receive a cookie or even to refuse cookies. However, you should know that some parts of bridedressup.net website can only be normally seen if your browser allows cookies.

bridedressup.net will not share your information with anyone. The only exception shall be in the event that disclosure of information is required by law enforcement or other government officials in connection with investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or that may expose you or us to legal liability. 

**Collection of information and Third-Party sites and Sponsors  
**It is important that you understand that advertisers or Web sites that link from bridedressup.net site may collect personal information about you. The Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of other advertisers or Web sites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our sites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other sites in order to help them provide relevant ads to users. Third parties may also be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on our website. If you do not wish for these third-parties to place and read cookies you can set your browser to block them.   

Google Adsense 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Security**  
All data that we collect is stored on one or more database servers. We are taking any reasonable precaution to secure the data, but you have to understand that the internet is not 100% safe and we cannot guarantee the safety of your information. All this kind of transmission whatsoever is made on your own risk.   
Links to Other Sites  
Our website has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. 

**AGREEMENT WITH bridedressup.net POLICIES**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the bridedressup.net Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use bridedressup.net site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our privacy policy will indicate the date it was last updated.
